Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Where have you been?
Hasn't your father told you
to come straight home after school?
Having fun tonight. boys?
I think you dropped something. no?
No?
Did you buy this inside?
-No. it's not ours.
-Don't worry. relax.
It's all good.
You boys are lucky.
You got your whole lives ahead of you.
You all leave.
Leave. Move fast.
I told you. you dumb motherfucker.
to watch his every move...
...and yet Amir Asif has grabbed my son.
We can negotiate.
This isn't about ransom. Saju.
It's about humiliation.
Go to Dhaka.
And do what?
Steal him back.
I'd need an army. Ovi.
Then hire a fucking army!
What do you think?
You think I can't hurt you from here?
Ovi. please...
You want your son
to see his next birthday?
Then...
get mine back.
Tell Mahajan to pay the ransom
and get his son back.
Why are they getting us involved in this?
Neysa...
There's not enough money.
The NCB have frozen Mahajan's assets.
There's a man who does this sort of thing.
His price will be out of Mahajan's reach.
But there's a way I can play this.
It will not be easy.
Do whatever you have to.
Proof.
Money.
Show me proof.
Money!
Bastard!
Didn't even blink!
Come on. boy!
Show me your face.
Beautiful!
Move it!
Let's go!
Sons of bitches.
Anybody feel like they remember now?
Wait!
I know...
I know who took the money.
Who?
-Sanjib.
-Who's Sanjib?
You just threw him off the roof.
Come here.
What's your name?
Farhad.
Farhad?
You're pretty clever.
Pay attention...
and learn...
that's how you survive.
You need to be smart. Use your wits.
Farhad?
Cut off two of your fingers.
Any two.
Why?
Because the kid who stole from me is dead.
And I'd like a walking reminder
of what happens when you touch my money.
I'd recommend the left hand.
So you can still hold a gun.
Amir!
I am talking!
Amir. we lost the kid.
Clever and lucky...
Close the city.
Bridges. trains. airports...
Close everything.
Impossible. Amir.
Make it possible. Colonel.
or you'll lose more than just a finger.
Blockades have been set up on
every bridge into and out of Dhaka.
I have teams combing
the Buriganga as we speak.
We'll find them. sir.
I like this one.
Get him a gun. Put his fingers to work.
Colonel. stand by.
We think we found something.
We need air support by the river.
They're in the forest.
Ovi. it's Saju!
I'm here to take you home!
Help! Help! Help!
Come here.
Come here. you little shit--
Are you hurt?
The vehicle crashed.
It flipped over and is in flames.
I want to see the bodies.
We're coming.
They're still alive.
One is seriously injured.
I want every gun in Dhaka
pointed at this guy.
Are you okay?
Listen to me carefully.
If you don't hear from me
in the next 12 hours.
take the cash and go.
Disappear.
I will...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Just tired.
Aarav. Papa's on the phone.
Are you coming home soon?
Yes. it'll be very soon.
When?
When you wake up in the morning.
You help your mother. okay?
Yes. Papa. I will.
-Hey. this guy wants my gun!
-My ankle is broken!
Leave my gun.
Leave it!
My friend is gonna shoot you!
Hey! Give me my gun... Give it back!
That's my gun. give it back to me!
Give it back or I'll blow you away!
Son of a bitch!
I'll kill you!
I'll murder you.
Don't you see I'm eating?
-I had him...
-Had who?
The man you want.
I lost him...
near the market.
Tell them to scour the market.
Yes. sir.
-What is this?
-A gift.
When you catch him.
I want to be the one to pull the trigger.
If you let me do that.
I'll give you the other finger!
He made me feel like a fool.
Of course he did.
You're only a kid.
Here's some advice. a gift.
Keep your other finger.
Because no matter how badass
you think you are...
there's always a badass
who's bigger than you.
Estancia Los Chanares.
We'll have to go on foot.
Any sign of the boy?
Not yet.
But we've seen our friend...
the kid must be near.
Don't cross the bridge.
I'm telling you to stop!
Take his hat off. Let me see his face.
I don't understand.
His hat. Take it off.
Do what he says.
Take two more units to the bridge.
Two units to the bridge. Hurry.
Bring me my rifle!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today